[
  {
    "question": "What have you eaten today?",
    "id": "0",
    "type": "Checkbox",
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Breakfast"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Second breakfast"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lunch"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Dinner"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you hungry?",
    "id": "1",
    "type": "Radio",
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "show": "2"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "hide": "2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you want an apple?",
    "id": "2",
    "type": "Radio",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "1",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Yes"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes"        
      },
      {
        "answer": "No"
      }
    ]
  },  
  {
    "question": "how was the apple?",
    "id": "3",
    "type": "Radio",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "2",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Yes"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Bad"
      },
      {
        "answer": "OK"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Good"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you Thirsty?",
    "id": "4",
    "type": "Radio",
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you want some water?",
    "id": "5",
    "type": "Radio",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "4",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Yes"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "how was the water?",
    "id": "6",
    "type": "Radio",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "5",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Yes"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Bad"
      },
      {
        "answer": "OK"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Good"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Did you feel hydrated?",
    "id": "7",
    "type": "Dropdown",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "6",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Good"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "scale of one to yum, how epic was the water",
    "id": "8",
    "type": "Slider",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "7",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Yes"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "how fun was drinking out of the glass",
    "id": "9",
    "type": "Slider", 
    "conditions": {
      "target": "8",
      "compare": ">",
      "value": 50
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you feel about what your thinking about right now",
    "id": "10",
    "type": "Emoji"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please list any other pleasant or unpleasant attributes of the water",
    "id": "11",
    "type": "Listing"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you enjoy this survey",
    "id": "12",
    "type": "YNifSo", 
    "ifSo": {
      "val": "Yes",
      "question": "What was the best part?"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you want to do it again?",
    "id": "13",
    "type": "Radio",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "12",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "Yes"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes"        
      },
      {
        "answer": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you want to go outside?",
    "id": "14",
    "type": "Radio",
    "conditions": {
      "target": "12",
      "compare": "=",
      "value": "No"
    },
    "responses": [
      {
        "answer": "Yes"        
      },
      {
        "answer": "No"
      }
    ]
  }
]
